<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<teacher-activity-cards lang="en">  <ac_card-1 day="1">    <ac_card-1_front>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_f_1" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>We Share</ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <instructions>
        <section-block type="instructions_f_1" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Instructions</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>        <before-section>
          <section-block type="before_f_1" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Connect to Large Group</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  <ac_teacher-speaking>Today we read the book <ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue>Thank You, Omu! </ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue>and we learned that Omu shared her delicious stew with her neighbors. When you share something, you let someone use or have it. Omu let her neighbors have all of her delicious soup.</ac_teacher-speaking></ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Explain the Activity  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>
              <ac_teacher-speaking>Today we are going to look at different pictures. Each picture shows people sharing different things. Look at the picture and say how the people in the pictures are sharing. </ac_teacher-speaking>
            </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </before-section>        <during-section>
          <section-block type="during_f_1" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Ask </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> Show one picture card and ask the question on the back of the card, offering extra challenge or support as needed.</ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Extend  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Use the last question on the back of the card to extend conversation.</ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Repeat</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  Continue the activity using the next picture card.  </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </during-section>        <after-section>
          <section-block type="after_f_1" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Talk About Sharing  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Ask children to think about other ways they can share with their friends and their families. Encourage children to use as many describing words as possible as they talk about sharing. Have children share things they find around the classroom. </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </after-section>      </instructions>    </ac_card-1_front>    <ac_card-1_back>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_b_1" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>We Share</ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>            <differentiation-section>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_1" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Differentiation</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>      <section-block type="differentiation_b_1" index="2">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Support</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Have children talk about what they see in the picture. Invite them to say what each person is doing. Then, ask them if they think one person is letting the other person use or have something.</ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_1" index="3">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Challenge</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Encourage children to participate in peer-to-peer conversations about sharing, with each child taking two turns in the conversation. Remind children that while one person is talking, the other is listening. </ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </differentiation-section>      <modifications-section>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_1" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Modifications</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_1" index="2">
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Multilingual Learners</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Young children are, in many ways, better at learning a new language than adults. Parents, for example, may be afraid that they will say something in English incorrectly. Young children, on the other hand, are less inhibited and willing to take risks. Create a stress-free environment in which children enjoy trying out new words, one where their home language and English are both celebrated.</ac_teacher-card-body>
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Focus Attention</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Preschoolers need to learn how to sustain attention during classroom activities. You can encourage attention by repeating the questions for each card and asking children to repeat the question. Improving children’s receptive vocabulary (listening comprehension) will help them sustain attention. Try and increase children’s vocabulary each week, using new vocabulary every day and providing safe opportunities to use those words on their own.</ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </modifications-section>      <copyright-section>
        <section-block type="copyright_b_1" index="1">
          <ac_back_copyright_line>
            <isbn>978-1-338-64914-7</isbn>. TM ® &amp; © Scholastic Inc. All rights reserved. </ac_back_copyright_line>
        </section-block>
      </copyright-section>    </ac_card-1_back>  </ac_card-1>  <ac_card-2 day="2">    <ac_card-2_front>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_f_2" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>I Share, You Share</ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <instructions>
        <section-block type="instructions_f_2" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Instructions</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>        <before-section>
          <section-block type="before_f_2" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Connect to Large Group</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  <ac_teacher-speaking>Today we read the book <ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue>Thank You, Omu! </ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue>We learned about looking at things in different ways. We learned that Omu gave all of her delicious stew to her neighbors because they were hungry. Omu was happy to share her delicious stew with her neighbors. But when the stew was finished, there was none left for Omu so she was sad. </ac_teacher-speaking></ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Explain the Activity</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  <ac_teacher-speaking>Today we will talk about how Omu was the one who shared her stew in the beginning and the neighbors were the ones who got the stew. Then at the end of the book, the neighbors gave food to Omu.</ac_teacher-speaking> </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </before-section>        <during-section>
          <section-block type="during_f_2" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Provide Prompts </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> Invite children to talk about what Omu did for her neighbors. Why did she give all of her stew to her neighbors? Then invite children to talk about what the neighbors did for Omu. Why did the neighbors give Omu food at the end of the book? </ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Encourage </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> At the end of the story, Omu was full of happiness and love. Encourage children to draw a picture that shows how Omu was feeling. They can add other characters or make up a story of their own with Omu sharing other things with her neighbors.</ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Write or Draw </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> Invite children to write or tell what their drawing shows.</ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </during-section>        <after-section>
          <section-block type="after_f_2" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Talk About Taking Different Perspectives  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Invite children to take turns pretending they are either Omu giving the food or receiving the neighbors food or that they are the neighbors receiving Omu’s food or giving Omu food.</ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </after-section>      </instructions>    </ac_card-2_front>    <ac_card-2_back>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_b_2" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>I Share, You Share</ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <differentiation-section>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_2" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Differentiation</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_2" index="2">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Support</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Check children’s understanding by modeling giving them an object and then asking them to give you an object in return. This will help children identify the roles of giving and receiving.</ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_2" index="3">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Challenge</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Encourage children to participate in peer-to-peer conversations about how Omu’s role changed by the end of the story. Remind children that while one person is talking, the other is listening.</ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </differentiation-section>      <modifications-section>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_2" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Modifications</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_2" index="2">
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Multilingual Learners</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Encourage multilingual learners to talk about their drawings and tell the story of what they drew. They may choose to use words from their home language in the captions that they dictate to you. If necessary, get help from other native speakers of that language.</ac_teacher-card-body>
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Taking Another Perspective</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Some children may struggle to learn how to take another person’s perspective. Using the example of finding different food delicious or not delicious might help children to see another’s perspective about the same thing. Say a food and have children raise their hands if they enjoy it. This will provide visual confirmation there are differences between their classmates and themselves. </ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </modifications-section>                  <copyright-section>
        <section-block type="copyright_b_2" index="1">
          <ac_back_copyright_line>
            <isbn>978-1-338-64914-7</isbn>. TM ® &amp; © Scholastic Inc. All rights reserved. </ac_back_copyright_line>
        </section-block>
      </copyright-section>    </ac_card-2_back>  </ac_card-2>  <ac_card-3 day="3">    <ac_card-3_front>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_f_3" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>act it and say it</ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <instructions>
        <section-block type="instructions_f_3" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Instructions</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>        <before-section>
          <section-block type="before_f_3" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Connect to Large Group</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  <ac_teacher-speaking>Today we read <ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue>Thank You, Omu! </ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue>again. There are a lot of interesting words and sentences in the story that will be fun to act out.</ac_teacher-speaking></ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Explain the Activity  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>
              <ac_teacher-speaking>In this activity, we will be actors. We will act out sentences from the story that the different people said. We will use our bodies and our voices.</ac_teacher-speaking>
            </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </before-section>        <during-section>
          <section-block type="during_f_3" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Using Body and Voice  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>For each quote below, turn to the page in the Big Book, point to the text and illustration, and read the text.  Show children how you are using your body gestures and your voice to show Omu tasting her stew and thinking that it is delicious. First, have children show the emotion or feeling without using any words. Then have children add in the words, repeating the sentences after you.</ac_teacher-card-body><ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Act Out and Repeat </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> Have children <ac_teacher-talk-emphasis>exclaim</ac_teacher-talk-emphasis>, “What a delicious stew!” (page 3); have children <ac_teacher-talk-emphasis>exclaim:</ac_teacher-talk-emphasis> “Little Boy! What brings you to my home?” (page 7); have children <ac_teacher-talk-emphasis>sigh:</ac_teacher-talk-emphasis> “MMMMM, STEW! That sure sounds yummy!” (page 7); have children <ac_teacher-talk-emphasis>lick their lips</ac_teacher-talk-emphasis> and then say: “OOOOO, STEW! That sounds quite delectable.” (page 18); and have children <ac_teacher-talk-emphasis>sniffle</ac_teacher-talk-emphasis> as they say: “There goes the best dinner I ever had!” (page 27).  </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </during-section>        <after-section>
          <section-block type="after_f_3" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Talk About It  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Tell children that writers use words like <ac_teacher-talk-emphasis>exclaim, sigh, </ac_teacher-talk-emphasis>and <ac_teacher-talk-emphasis>sniffle</ac_teacher-talk-emphasis> to help readers understand the story. Help children choose new sentences and say them in different ways—they can exclaim it, say it loudly or softly, say it with a sad voice, or say it with a happy voice.</ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </after-section>      </instructions>    </ac_card-3_front>    <ac_card-3_back>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_b_3" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>act it and say it</ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <differentiation-section>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_3" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Differentiation</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_3" index="2">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Support</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Before children say the sentence, explain what the words <ac_teacher-talk-emphasis>exclaim, sigh,</ac_teacher-talk-emphasis> and <ac_teacher-talk-emphasis>sniffle</ac_teacher-talk-emphasis> mean. Model them. Then invite children to say the sentence modeling your expressions. </ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_3" index="3">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Challenge</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Have children repeat the phrases with different emotions. For example, instead of Omu feeling sad and sniffling, she could be really angry when she discovers her pot is empty. How would they change their faces, bodies, and voices to show anger?</ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </differentiation-section>      <modifications-section>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_3" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Modifications</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_3" index="2">
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Multilingual Learners</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Humans learn grammar through oral language models. Subject-verb agreement is an abstract concept even for older children. It helps to lay a good foundation for children to learn the grammar of academic language during these early years.  If a child says something incorrectly, such as, “They was eating,” respond by repeating the statement correctly, such as, “Yes. They were eating.”</ac_teacher-card-body>
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Speech Support</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>If children have speech difficulties, allow them to act out the story without repeating the full sentences or just repeating certain words like “Yummy!” Help children practice their speech in safe settings, while giving them nonverbal ways to communicate when they appear tired or frustrated. </ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </modifications-section>                  <copyright-section>
        <section-block type="copyright_b_3" index="1">
          <ac_back_copyright_line>
            <isbn>978-1-338-64914-7</isbn>. TM ® &amp; © Scholastic Inc. All rights reserved. </ac_back_copyright_line>
        </section-block>
      </copyright-section>    </ac_card-3_back>  </ac_card-3>  <ac_card-4 day="4">    <ac_card-4_front>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_f_4" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>Who works here? </ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <instructions>
        <section-block type="instructions_f_4" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Instructions</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>        <before-section>
          <section-block type="before_f_4" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Gather Materials</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  You will need the Big Chart of Big Ideas and <ac_teacher-talk-emphasis>Thank you, Omu!</ac_teacher-talk-emphasis></ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Connect to Large Group</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  <ac_teacher-speaking>Today we read the poster <ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue>Super Jobs. </ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue>We learned about the jobs each of these people do in their community. Earlier this week, we read the book <ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue>Thank you, Omu!</ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue> We read about people who have different jobs in Omu’s community, like the police officer, the bus driver, the doctor, and the baker.</ac_teacher-speaking></ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Explain the Activity  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>
              <ac_teacher-speaking>Today, we will look at pictures of different places and try to guess who works there. It could be the baker, the bus driver, the doctor, or any of the people we read about this week.</ac_teacher-speaking>
            </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </before-section>        <during-section>
          <section-block type="during_f_4" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Ask  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Show one picture card and ask the question on the back of the card, offering extra challenge or support as needed.</ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Extend</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  Use the last question on the back of the card to extend conversation.</ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Repeat</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  Continue the activity using the next picture card.  </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </during-section>        <after-section>
          <section-block type="after_f_4" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Talk About Jobs  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Invite children to think about other jobs people have in their communities. You can remind children about the different jobs in their community by reviewing the Big Chart and reviewing the different jobs in <ac_teacher-talk>Thank You, Omu!</ac_teacher-talk> (page 22).</ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </after-section>      </instructions>    </ac_card-4_front>    <ac_card-4_back>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_b_4" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>Who works here? </ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <differentiation-section>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_4" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Differentiation</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_4" index="2">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Support</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Have children describe what they see in the picture. If there is a person in the picture, ask them to describe what the person is doing. This will help children identify the link between the location and the person who might work there.</ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_4" index="3">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Challenge</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Ask children to think of other places where they might see the people in the pictures. For example, a firefighter works at a fire station, but you might see him or her putting out a fire. </ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </differentiation-section>      <modifications-section>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_4" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Modifications</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_4" index="2">
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Multilingual Learners</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Model and encourage children to use a physical response, in addition to speaking, to talk about the what the different people do in their jobs. For example, they can hold their hands out to show a firefighter using a hose to put out a fire. Or they can pretend to write on a board like a teacher would. </ac_teacher-card-body>
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Support Conversation Skills</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>One conversation strategy is to restate what a child has said and then immediately ask: <ac_teacher-talk>Is that what you meant?</ac_teacher-talk> By restating what a child has said, you validate their contributions, make sure that you understood the child correctly, and model correct language. Eventually, you can have children restate what their classmates have said using the same method. Children will listen more closely to their classmates if they know that you may ask for volunteers to restate what the classmate just said.</ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </modifications-section>                  <copyright-section>
        <section-block type="copyright_b_4" index="1">
          <ac_back_copyright_line>
            <isbn>978-1-338-64914-7</isbn>. TM ® &amp; © Scholastic Inc. All rights reserved. </ac_back_copyright_line>
        </section-block>
      </copyright-section>    </ac_card-4_back>  </ac_card-4>            </teacher-activity-cards>
