<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<flip-chart lang="en">
  <flip_chart-12 day="4">
    <flip_chart-12_front>
      <graphic href="EC3-5_Flipchart_T3W4_TheGreatBigEnormousYucca.jpg"/>
    </flip_chart-12_front>
    <flip_chart-12_back>
      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_b_1" index="1">
          <flip_chart-theme-text>LET’s INVESTIGATE</flip_chart-theme-text>
          <flip_chart-topic-text>Make It Move</flip_chart-topic-text>
          <flip_chart-concept-question>How can we make things go?</flip_chart-concept-question>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>
      <display-head-section>
        <section-block type="display_b_1" index="1">
          <flip_chart-display-head>The Great Big Enormous Yuca</flip_chart-display-head>
        </section-block>
      </display-head-section>
      <teacher-facing-section>
        <section-block type="teacher-facing_b_1" index="1">
          <flip_chart-teacher-facing-content-box>
            <flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Once upon a time, an old man planted a yuca. “Grow, little yuca, grow,” he said, “until you are enormous and sweet and delicious.”</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>The next day, the old man saw that the little plant had grown into the biggest he had ever seen. He couldn’t wait to cook the yuca for dinner. So he started to pull. <flip_chart-bold>The old man pulled and pulled.</flip_chart-bold> But the enormous yuca would not come up. </flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>He called to his wife. “Sofia! Come help me pull up this yuca, so we can have it for our dinner.” So, <flip_chart-bold>the old woman pulled the old man.</flip_chart-bold> And the old man pulled the yuca. They pulled and pulled. But the enormous yuca would not come up.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>The old woman called to her granddaughter. “Ana! Come and help us pull this enormous yuca, so we can have it for our dinner.” So, <flip_chart-bold>Ana pulled the old woman.</flip_chart-bold> And the old woman pulled the old man. And the old man pulled the yuca. They pulled and they pulled. But the enormous yuca would not come up.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Ana called to her dog. “Perro! Come help us pull this enormous yuca so we can have it for our dinner!” So, <flip_chart-bold>the dog pulled Ana</flip_chart-bold>. And Ana pulled the old woman. And the old woman pulled the old man. They pulled and they pulled. But the enormous yuca would still not come up.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>“How will we ever enjoy this delicious treat?” they wondered.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Just then a little mouse came by and asked if he could help. “But you are so little!” said the family. Still, the mouse wanted to help. So, <flip_chart-bold>the mouse pulled the dog</flip_chart-bold>. The dog pulled Ana. Ana pulled the old woman. And the old woman pulled the old man. They pulled and they pulled. <flip_chart-bold>The enormous yuca finally came up!</flip_chart-bold> </flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>That night they all enjoyed a delicious yuca stew for their dinner.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>
          </flip_chart-teacher-facing-content-box>
        </section-block>
      </teacher-facing-section>
      <copyright-section>
        <section-block type="copyright_b_1" index="1">
          <flip_chart-credit-line>Illustration by Carolina Farias, © Scholastic Inc.</flip_chart-credit-line>
        </section-block>
      </copyright-section>
    </flip_chart-12_back>
  </flip_chart-12>
</flip-chart>
