<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<flip-chart lang="en">
  <flip_chart-7 day="4">
    <flip_chart-7_front>
      <graphic href="EC3-5_Flipchart_T2W3_SuperJobs.jpg"/>
    </flip_chart-7_front>
    <flip_chart-7_back>
      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_b_1" index="1">
          <flip_chart-theme-text>OUR COMMUNITY</flip_chart-theme-text>
          <flip_chart-topic-text>Helpers</flip_chart-topic-text>
          <flip_chart-concept-question>Who are the people who help in our community?</flip_chart-concept-question>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>
      <display-head-section>
        <section-block type="display_b_1" index="1">
          <flip_chart-display-head>Super Jobs</flip_chart-display-head>
        </section-block>
      </display-head-section>
      <teacher-facing-section>
        <section-block type="teacher-facing_b_1" index="1">
          <flip_chart-teacher-facing-content-box>
            <flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>All around our community, workers are doing important jobs that help us! Let’s find out who some of these workers are!</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-head>Doctor</flip_chart-teacher-facing-head><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>
              <flip_chart-emphasis>Ahhhchoo!</flip_chart-emphasis> Who can you call when you are sick in bed, sniffling and feeling achy? A doctor!</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>A doctor’s important job is to help keep your body healthy. When you are sick, a doctor can tell you what to do to help you feel better.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>But you don’t only visit a doctor when you are sick. The most important part of the doctor’s job is to help you stay healthy! That is why you have checkups. A doctor uses different tools to check how each part of your body is working. A doctor uses a stethoscope to listen to your heart. He or she looks at your throat and checks your ears. The doctor also tells you how to eat right and exercise. All of these things will keep you healthy, so that you can learn and play. Thank you, doctors!</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-head>Plumber</flip_chart-teacher-facing-head><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>You use water every day. Water comes into your home through pipes, and it leaves your home through pipes. We have pipes in our kitchens and in our bathrooms. Who helps to make sure the pipes work well? A plumber!</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Sometimes, a water pipe is blocked and no water will come out or go down. Then it’s time to call the plumber! The plumber uses tools to open up the pipe and clear it out. </flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Now turn on the faucet! You have water to drink, water to wash with, and water to cook with. Thank you, plumbers!</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-head>Baker</flip_chart-teacher-facing-head><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Do you like bread and pies and cookies? What about birthday cake? Bakers make all of these.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Bakers mix together ingredients like flour, eggs, and sugar. This mixture is called dough. Do you ever play with colorful play dough? A baker’s dough is almost the same, except you can eat it.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Bakers shape the dough into loaves of bread, cookies that look like stars or hearts, or cakes with many layers! Then they put the dough into the oven until it is cooked.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>A bakery is warm inside, and the shelves are filled with colorful and delicious treats. Yum! Thank you, bakers!</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-head>Firefighter</flip_chart-teacher-facing-head><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>
              <flip_chart-emphasis>Wee-o-wee-o-wee-oo!</flip_chart-emphasis> A siren blasts down the street. A long red truck comes rushing by. Its red and white lights are flashing. There’s an emergency in the neighborhood, and the firefighters are coming to the rescue!</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>These important workers help to keep us safe. When a fire breaks out, firefighters rush to put on their fire clothes and grab their equipment. Then they hop onto the truck and rush to put out the fire!</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>The fire truck has lots of equipment that firefighters use to do their jobs. There are long hoses that squirt water to put out fires. There are tall ladders that can stretch to the top floor of a building. A firefighter might have to climb a ladder to rescue someone who is stuck inside. When the fire is out, the firefighters go back to the fire station. There they can eat and relax. But they are always ready for the next alarm, so they can hop onto the fire truck and come to the rescue. Thank you, firefighters!</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>
          </flip_chart-teacher-facing-content-box>
        </section-block>
      </teacher-facing-section>
      <copyright-section>
        <section-block type="copyright_b_1" index="1">
          <flip_chart-credit-line>Photos ©: background: DarkPlatypus/Shutterstock; top right: LightField Studios/Shutterstock; top left: Michael H/Getty Images; bottom left: Ariel Skelley/Getty Images; bottom right: avid_creative/Getty Images; Icons by Wook Jin Jung for Scholastic.</flip_chart-credit-line>
        </section-block>
      </copyright-section>
    </flip_chart-7_back>
  </flip_chart-7>
</flip-chart>
