<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<flip-chart lang="en">
  <flip_chart-23 day="4">
    <flip_chart-23_front>
      <graphic href="EC3-5_Flipchart_T6W3_AHorseOfCourse.jpg"/>
    </flip_chart-23_front>
    <flip_chart-23_back>
      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_b_1" index="1">
          <flip_chart-theme-text>Let’s Create</flip_chart-theme-text>
          <flip_chart-topic-text>Picture This</flip_chart-topic-text>
          <flip_chart-concept-question>How can we express ourselves through making art?</flip_chart-concept-question>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>
      <display-head-section>
        <section-block type="display_b_1" index="1">
          <flip_chart-display-head>A Horse, of Course</flip_chart-display-head>
        </section-block>
      </display-head-section>
      <teacher-facing-section>
        <section-block type="teacher-facing_b_1" index="1">
          <flip_chart-teacher-facing-content-box>
            <flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Artists have been interested in horses for many years. These beautiful and powerful creatures can help people travel from one place to another. They can carry heavy loads. And they can help farmers plow fields. There are many different ways artists can show their love of horses.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>
            <flip_chart-teacher-facing-head>Draw It.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-head>
            <flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>People who lived in caves long ago didn’t have paper, so they left messages for each other on the cave walls. Since there was no alphabet, they used drawings to communicate. Many drawings were of animals. They drew horses, bison, boars, mammoths, and deer. If you drew a horse, what would it look like?</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>
            <flip_chart-teacher-facing-head>Paint It.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-head>
            <flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Some artists like to use paint and brushes to make pictures of horses. The horse in this painting is running on a beach. The artist colored this horse using different paints. If you painted a horse, what colors would you use?</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>
            <flip_chart-teacher-facing-head>Sculpt It.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-head>
            <flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Other artists create art by carving or molding animals or objects out of different materials. Those are called sculptures. These mustang sculptures were made out of bronze. The artist made the horses look like they were running across a stream. If you sculpted a horse, what material would you use?</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>
          </flip_chart-teacher-facing-content-box>
        </section-block>
      </teacher-facing-section>
      <copyright-section>
        <section-block type="copyright_b_1" index="1">
          <flip_chart-credit-line>Photos ©: Shutterstock: top left (Charbonnier Thierry), top right (Alexey Kashin), center left (Irina Baturina), center right (vvoe), bottom right (Lubos Chlubny), aged wood texture (Nella), nails (donatas1205), brown wood texture (nexus 7); Paul Lee/Alamy Images: bottom left.</flip_chart-credit-line>
        </section-block>
      </copyright-section>
    </flip_chart-23_back>
  </flip_chart-23>
</flip-chart>
