<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<teacher-activity-cards lang="en">  <ac_card-1 day="1">    <ac_card-1_front>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_f_1" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>A-B-CELEBRATE!</ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <instructions>
        <section-block type="instructions_f_1" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Instructions</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>        <before-section>
          <section-block type="before_f_1" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Connect to Large Group  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>
              <ac_teacher-speaking>Today we read <ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue>Imagine</ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue> by Juan Herrera. Juan wrote the story in a poem. When he was a young boy, Juan used his imagination as he explored nature and helped on the farm. At school, his imagination and his love for words helped him learn English and become a writer of stories and songs. When he grew up, Juan became an award-winning poet. You are learning to read and write, too! Let’s celebrate what you’ve learned about letters.</ac_teacher-speaking></ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Explain the Activity  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>
              <ac_teacher-speaking>We’re going to make a human alphabet! </ac_teacher-speaking>
            </ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-teacher_talk_bulleted>
              <ac_teacher-speaking>I’m going to name a letter. Work as a team to decide how to make that letter—using YOU! You will form the shape of the letter with your bodies. </ac_teacher-speaking>
            </ac_teacher-card-teacher_talk_bulleted>
            <ac_teacher-card-teacher_talk_bulleted>
              <ac_teacher-speaking>I will take a picture of each letter, and we will hang up our new alphabet in the classroom.</ac_teacher-speaking>
            </ac_teacher-card-teacher_talk_bulleted>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Model/Teach </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> Tell children you’ll start by forming the letter <ac_teacher-talk>T</ac_teacher-talk>. Before this activity, observe your school’s procedures for receiving permission for taking pictures of the children. If you don’t have permission, modify the activity by having children draw the letters.   </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </before-section>        <during-section>
          <section-block type="during_f_1" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Ask</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  <ac_teacher-speaking>What letter are you making? What sound does that letter make? </ac_teacher-speaking>Encourage children to connect the letter with the sound/sounds it makes.</ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Repeat  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Repeat for each letter. Take a photo of children in their letter shapes before they move on to the next one.</ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Extend  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Ask children to name a word that starts with each letter.    </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </during-section>        <after-section>
          <section-block type="after_f_1" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Talk About Achievements</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  Encourage children to feel pride in how much they’ve learned and share which letters they like best. </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </after-section>      </instructions>    </ac_card-1_front>    <ac_card-1_back>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_b_1" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>A-B-CELEBRATE!</ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>            <differentiation-section>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_1" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Differentiation</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>      <section-block type="differentiation_b_1" index="2">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Support</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Use this activity as a way to assess end-of-year alphabet knowledge. Revisit any letters that children do not seem to recognize, and provide extra help as needed. You may also pair children with those who are more comfortable with the letters and encourage peer learning.</ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_1" index="3">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Challenge</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>If children find the activity easy, challenge them to form entire words using their bodies. Take pictures of those, too. </ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </differentiation-section>      <modifications-section>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_1" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Modifications</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_1" index="2">
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Multilingual Learners</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Multilingual learners may have difficulty due to the kinesthetic nature of this activity and might have trouble quickly recalling letters from the English alphabet instead of ones from their home language. Before the activity, take the time to review each letter with the Alphabet Cards, allowing children the opportunity to see and visualize each letter. </ac_teacher-card-body>
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Gross Motor Skills</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>If physical challenges prevent children from forming letter shapes using their bodies, set these children up to succeed in another way. Allow them to form a letter another way. Or have them perform a different task, such as telling classmates which letter to form, or taking a picture of the finished product. </ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </modifications-section>      <copyright-section>
        <section-block type="copyright_b_1" index="1">
          <ac_back_copyright_line>
            <isbn>978-1-338-65581-0</isbn>. TM ® &amp; © Scholastic Inc. All rights reserved. </ac_back_copyright_line>
        </section-block>
      </copyright-section>    </ac_card-1_back>  </ac_card-1>  <ac_card-2 day="2">    <ac_card-2_front>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_f_2" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>SHOW What you can do!</ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <instructions>
        <section-block type="instructions_f_2" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Instructions</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>        <before-section>
          <section-block type="before_f_2" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Connect to Large Group </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> <ac_teacher-speaking>Today we reread the narrative poem <ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue>Imagine. </ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue>We talked about self-awareness and how Juan knew what he was good at: writing stories and poems!</ac_teacher-speaking></ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Explain the Activity </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>
              <ac_teacher-speaking> Today we are going to have a talent show! You can show the class something you are good at. Think about something you love. Maybe you have a favorite song you sing, or you can draw something well. Maybe you are a great dancer! Take a few minutes to practice your talent. I’ll show you mine, too! </ac_teacher-speaking>
            </ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Review the Mind Builder</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  Talk with children about things they can do.</ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Model/Teach</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  Share a talent you may have with the class. After you present, talk about when you realized this was an ability you had.   </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </before-section>        <during-section>
          <section-block type="during_f_2" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Ask</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  As each child finishes showing their talent, ask questions that provide them with an opportunity to express an opinion of their abilities: <ac_teacher-speaking>Did someone teach you how to do this, or did you figure it out on your own? When did you first realize you were so good at this? Can you show me how to do that?</ac_teacher-speaking> Encourage the children in the audience to offer positive feedback.</ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Extend  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Compliment children on knowing their strengths. Explain that this shows they are really growing up. Ask children to tell why it may be important to talk about abilities that may need to work on, too.    </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </during-section>        <after-section>
          <section-block type="after_f_2" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Talk about Pride</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  Start a conversation by telling children that you are proud of how hard they have worked this year in school. Explain that the class has just shown how each person has their own talents and abilities. Encourage confidence by telling children that differences are what make us special. They are something to be proud of. </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </after-section>      </instructions>    </ac_card-2_front>    <ac_card-2_back>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_b_2" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>SHOW what you can do!</ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <differentiation-section>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_2" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Differentiation</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_2" index="2">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Support</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>If children struggle to think of a talent or ability, guide them by reminding them of something you have seen them do well. You may need to take a few one-on-one minutes to help them prepare. </ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_2" index="3">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Challenge</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>If children would like an extra challenge, offer them the chance to announce each child as they come on the “stage” to perform. </ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </differentiation-section>      <modifications-section>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_2" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Modifications</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_2" index="2">
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Multilingual Learners</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Multilingual learners may be shy and not want to share their talents, especially if it involves an extensive amount of English vocabulary. Tell children at least one day before the talent show, so they can have some time to prepare and feel comfortable. Additionally, you may wish to allow children to perform or share their talents in their home language, giving children the opportunity to feel confident in their talents.</ac_teacher-card-body>
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Emotional Support</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Children with social anxiety may recoil at the idea of performing in front of a class, or even sharing their opinion on their work. However, oral presentations will be a large part of their academic careers. This activity will introduce them to the idea in a more comfortable setting.</ac_teacher-card-body>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>You know best if this activity will overwhelm anxious children in your class. If so, allow them to draw a picture of their talent, to share.</ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </modifications-section>                  <copyright-section>
        <section-block type="copyright_b_2" index="1">
          <ac_back_copyright_line>
            <isbn>978-1-338-65581-0</isbn>. TM ® &amp; © Scholastic Inc. All rights reserved. </ac_back_copyright_line>
        </section-block>
      </copyright-section>    </ac_card-2_back>  </ac_card-2>  <ac_card-3 day="3">    <ac_card-3_front>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_f_3" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>sounds like . . . ?</ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <instructions>
        <section-block type="instructions_f_3" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Instructions</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>        <before-section>
          <section-block type="before_f_3" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Connect to Large Group </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>
              <ac_teacher-speaking> Today we talked about Spanish being Juan’s first language. When he started school, he could not speak English. Imagine not understanding what anyone is saying!  </ac_teacher-speaking>
            </ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Explain the Activity  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>
              <ac_teacher-speaking>Today we are going to communicate without words. We will use only our bodies! We will take turns acting out and guessing.</ac_teacher-speaking>
            </ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-teacher_talk_bulleted>
              <ac_teacher-speaking>First, let’s divide into two teams. One will act out the activity and one will guess.</ac_teacher-speaking>
            </ac_teacher-card-teacher_talk_bulleted>
            <ac_teacher-card-teacher_talk_bulleted>
              <ac_teacher-speaking>I will whisper to one player something that Juan does in the book, such as letting tadpoles swim over his hands in the stream. The player will act out the scene. The other team works together to figure out the scene being acted out. Then, I will choose a player from the guessing team to act out a scene.   </ac_teacher-speaking>
            </ac_teacher-card-teacher_talk_bulleted>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Model/Teach </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> Remind children that there are many ways to communicate. Using our faces and bodies is a great way to communicate with someone when we don’t speak the same language.    </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </before-section>        <during-section>
          <section-block type="during_f_3" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Ask</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  After a group has guessed the correct answer, ask the questions on the back of the card to strengthen children’s cognitive skills. </ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Extend </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> Continue to play, using other scenes from the book or events from class.     </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </during-section>        <after-section>
          <section-block type="after_f_3" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Talk About Learning Languages</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  Emphasize the idea that children speak different languages all around the world. Tell children that one day, they may travel to a new place. Learning other languages will make it easier to make new friends! </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </after-section>      </instructions>    </ac_card-3_front>    <ac_card-3_back>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_b_3" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>sounds like . . . ?</ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <differentiation-section>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_3" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Differentiation</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_3" index="2">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Support</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>If children have trouble acting out a scene, suggest ways they might do it, or allow them to work with a partner. If children have a hard time guessing, allow them to ask questions and have the actors nod, shake their head, or use their face to show whether the question is correct.</ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_3" index="3">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Challenge</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>If children finish this activity easily, think of some more difficult things for children to act out and challenge them to complete the activity at a higher level. </ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </differentiation-section>      <modifications-section>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_3" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Modifications</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_3" index="2">
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Multilingual Learners</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>If children in your class speak Spanish as a first language, encourage them to identify the scene from the book using Spanish if they want to. Celebrate the diversity of language in your classroom!</ac_teacher-card-body>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Encourage children whose first language is neither English nor Spanish to act out scenes from the book or from other events in the classroom. Doing so will enhance a sense of social and global connection between all children. </ac_teacher-card-body>
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Gross Motor Development</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>If physical challenges prevent children from acting out the scene, modify the activity by letting children do something different, such as drawing images on paper. Set children up for success by allowing them to choose what makes them feel most comfortable. </ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </modifications-section>                  <copyright-section>
        <section-block type="copyright_b_3" index="1">
          <ac_back_copyright_line>
            <isbn>978-1-338-65581-0</isbn>. TM ® &amp; © Scholastic Inc. All rights reserved. </ac_back_copyright_line>
        </section-block>
      </copyright-section>    </ac_card-3_back>  </ac_card-3>  <ac_card-4 day="4">    <ac_card-4_front>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_f_4" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>I WANT TO . . . </ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <instructions>
        <section-block type="instructions_f_4" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Instructions</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>        <before-section>
          <section-block type="before_f_4" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Gather Materials </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> dress-up clothes, pretend play props</ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Connect to Large Group  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>
              <ac_teacher-speaking>Today we talked about imagining something you might want to do or be in the future. Now we’re going to play a game where you dress up as what you want to be. </ac_teacher-speaking>
            </ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Explain the Activity  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>
              <ac_teacher-speaking>Let’s pretend you are all grown up. You used your imagination, worked hard in school, and you have your dream job! Now you’re back to visit your old teacher. Don’t tell me what your job is. I will ask questions and you can answer. I will have to guess it!</ac_teacher-speaking> </ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Model/Teach  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Model the idea. For example, you might carry a baseball bat and wear a cap and talk about your team a lot. Allow children to guess that you have become a baseball player! Let children dress up and take a turn.    </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </before-section>        <during-section>
          <section-block type="during_f_4" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Ask</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  Encourage children to have fun and be creative. Welcome them and thank them for visiting. Then, ask as if interviewing: <ac_teacher-speaking>So what do you do in your job? Do you like it? Where do you live? </ac_teacher-speaking> </ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Repeat </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> Repeat until each child has had a turn. </ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Extend </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> Ask children, <ac_teacher-speaking>What made you want to become a<fill-in-the-blank>                </fill-in-the-blank>?</ac_teacher-speaking>     </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </during-section>        <after-section>
          <section-block type="after_f_4" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Talk About Perseverance</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  Explain that it takes hard work to make something you imagine become real. Impart a message of hope and inspiration: anyone can become what they want to be with enough hard work. Emphasize this point by talking about how Juan worked hard at everything he did. If time permits, let children remain in character and socialize as their future selves.  </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </after-section>      </instructions>    </ac_card-4_front>    <ac_card-4_back>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_b_4" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>I WANT TO . . . </ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <differentiation-section>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_4" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Differentiation</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_4" index="2">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Support</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>If children struggle to think of what they’d like to be or to find props, ask a friend to suggest one for them: <ac_teacher-talk>I’m sure you have an idea of what she might like to be! We’re stuck. What ideas do you have?  </ac_teacher-talk>
          </ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_4" index="3">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Challenge</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>For children who need an extra challenge, ask more difficult questions while they are in character: <ac_teacher-talk>Tell me about the work you did to get where you are. What did you have to do?</ac_teacher-talk> Don’t expect correct answers, but instead listen as children delve further into pretend play.</ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </differentiation-section>      <modifications-section>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_4" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Modifications</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_4" index="2">
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Multilingual Learners</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>If multilingual learners have difficulty answering interview questions about their dream job, provide sentence stems, such as <ac_teacher-talk>“At my job, I</ac_teacher-talk>
            <fill-in-the-blank>              </fill-in-the-blank>
            <ac_teacher-talk>”</ac_teacher-talk> or <ac_teacher-talk>“I like my job because</ac_teacher-talk>
            <fill-in-the-blank>              </fill-in-the-blank>
            <ac_teacher-talk>.”</ac_teacher-talk> Help them feel comfortable and confident in their interview by giving them different ways they can share about their dream job. </ac_teacher-card-body>
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Attention Support</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>This is a fun activity. The room may be high energy while it is taking place. Children with attention or anxiety issues may find it difficult to focus. Before they become overwhelmed, set them up for success by assigning them tasks to help them focus: let them carry props or clothes back to their bins. </ac_teacher-card-body>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Giving children something to occupy their hands while they sit and wait their turn can also help them avoid over-stimulation and maintain a focus. A spinner or other tool can be helpful in such situations. </ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </modifications-section>                  <copyright-section>
        <section-block type="copyright_b_4" index="1">
          <ac_back_copyright_line>
            <isbn>978-1-338-65581-0</isbn>. TM ® &amp; © Scholastic Inc. All rights reserved. </ac_back_copyright_line>
        </section-block>
      </copyright-section>    </ac_card-4_back>  </ac_card-4>            </teacher-activity-cards>
