<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<flip-chart lang="en">
  <flip_chart-29 day="4">
    <flip_chart-29_front>
      <graphic href="EC3-5_Flipchart_T8W1_WeHaveSoup.jpg"/>
    </flip_chart-29_front>
    <flip_chart-29_back>
      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_b_1" index="1">
          <flip_chart-theme-text>Ready, Set, Go</flip_chart-theme-text>
          <flip_chart-topic-text>We Can Do It</flip_chart-topic-text>
          <flip_chart-concept-question>What can we do better together?</flip_chart-concept-question>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>
      <display-head-section>
        <section-block type="display_b_1" index="1">
          <flip_chart-display-head>We Have Soup!</flip_chart-display-head>
        </section-block>
      </display-head-section>
      <teacher-facing-section>
        <section-block type="teacher-facing_b_1" index="1">
          <flip_chart-teacher-facing-content-box>
            <flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>It was winter. Claudia Rabbit was tired of the cold weather. She was tired of staying inside. But mostly she was tired of eating celery. She ate celery for breakfast, lunch, and dinner.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>
            <flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>“How can I turn this celery into something more delicious?” she wondered. </flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>
            <flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>As she munched on a stalk of celery, she had an idea. She brought a big pot to the center of Rabbitville. She filled the pot with water, sliced up a stalk of celery, put it into the pot, and began to cook it.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>
            <flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Carlos Rabbit and his baby sister Clara Rabbit passed by. “What are you making?” asked Carlos Rabbit.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>
            <flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>“I am making a vegetable soup,” said Claudia Rabbit. “Right now it only has the celery I grew in my garden. But other vegetables would make it even more delicious.”</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>
            <flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>“Oh!” said Carlos Rabbit. “<flip_chart-bold>We have peas.</flip_chart-bold> We have been eating peas all winter long. I know they will taste better if we add them to your soup!”</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>
            <flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Carlos and his sister Clara added the peas to the soup. Claudia stirred and stirred the soup.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>  <flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Soon, more rabbits heard about the soup. Philip Rabbit and his brother Ethan Rabbit walked by.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph> <flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>“<flip_chart-bold>We have corn</flip_chart-bold>,” they said. “We have been eating corn all winter long. The corn will taste much better if we add it to your soup.”</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph> <flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Claudia Rabbit added the corn and stirred the soup. It smelled better than ever. </flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Soon Larry Rabbit and his cousin Brenda Rabbit passed by.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>“What are you making?” he asked.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>“I am making vegetable soup,” said Claudia Rabbit. “Now it has celery, peas, and corn. But other vegetables would make the soup even more delicious!”</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph> <flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>“Oh!” said Larry Rabbit. “<flip_chart-bold>We have carrots.</flip_chart-bold> We have been eating carrots all winter long. We know our carrots will taste better if we add them to the soup!”</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Larry Rabbit and Brenda Rabbit added their carrots to the soup. Claudia Rabbit stirred the pot. The delicious smell of the soup floated through Rabbitville. </flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>More and more rabbits came. Each rabbit brought the vegetable they had been eating all winter long. Claudia Rabbit added all of the vegetables to the soup. It got thicker and smelled even better. At last the soup was ready! Everyone gathered around the giant pot.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph> <flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>“Look!” said Claudia Rabbit. “<flip_chart-bold>We have soup!</flip_chart-bold>”</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>She served each rabbit a big bowl of vegetable soup. They all agreed that it was the best soup ever.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>“Hooray for Claudia Rabbit!” they cheered. “<flip_chart-bold>Hooray for vegetable soup!</flip_chart-bold>”</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>And from that day on, the rabbits shared the vegetables they grew. They learned that they loved to cook different foods. They made vegetable soup, vegetable stew, vegetable sandwiches, and vegetable pie. And each dish was more delicious than the last because they made it together.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>
          </flip_chart-teacher-facing-content-box>
        </section-block>
      </teacher-facing-section>
      <copyright-section>
        <section-block type="copyright_b_1" index="1">
          <flip_chart-credit-line>Illustrations by Seth Adams, © Scholastic Inc.</flip_chart-credit-line>
        </section-block>
      </copyright-section>
    </flip_chart-29_back>
  </flip_chart-29>
</flip-chart>
