<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<teacher-activity-cards lang="en">  <ac_card-1 day="1">    <ac_card-1_front>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_f_1" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>TALK ABOUT TIME</ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <instructions>
        <section-block type="instructions_f_1" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Instructions</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>        <before-section>
          <section-block type="before_f_1" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Connect to Large Group </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> <ac_teacher-speaking>Today we read the book <ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue>How Kids Grow.</ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue> We learned that babies are little and are good at sleeping! They can already grasp someone’s fingers. As they grow they learn to do things like smile, roll, crawl, and stand. Later they can draw, play with toys, and build with blocks. Children learn to walk, then to run and hop and skip. They may learn how to ride a tricycle. Most children learn to ride a tricycle before they learn how to ride a bike.</ac_teacher-speaking></ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Explain the Activity </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>
              <ac_teacher-speaking> In this activity, we will look at pictures and talk about time. We’ll talk about what we do first and what we do next. We’ll think about what we learned yesterday and what we learned last week.</ac_teacher-speaking>
            </ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Teach/Model </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> <ac_teacher-speaking>Let’s look at this first card. What do we see? What is this girl eating? That’s right. She’s eating breakfast. What will her next meal be? When do we usually eat breakfast: in the morning, in the afternoon, or at night?</ac_teacher-speaking>    </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </before-section>        <during-section>
          <section-block type="during_f_1" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Ask </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> Show the next picture card and ask the question on the back of the card, offering extra challenge or support as needed.</ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Extend </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> Use the final question on the back of the card to extend conversation.</ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Repeat </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> Continue the activity using the rest of the picture cards, as time permits.  </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </during-section>        <after-section>
          <section-block type="after_f_1" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Talk About Time </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> Help children use language to describe the passing of time. Discuss the daily schedule with children, using terms such as “before lunch we will ...” and “after recess today we will ....” Engage children in a “daily news” dialogue, discussing each day’s events. </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </after-section>      </instructions>    </ac_card-1_front>    <ac_card-1_back>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_b_1" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>TALK ABOUT TIME</ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>            <differentiation-section>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_1" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Differentiation</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>      <section-block type="differentiation_b_1" index="2">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Support</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Check children’s understanding of <ac_teacher-talk>before</ac_teacher-talk> and <ac_teacher-talk>after, first, next,</ac_teacher-talk> and <ac_teacher-talk>last, longer than, </ac_teacher-talk>and things that take <ac_teacher-talk>less time</ac_teacher-talk> and <ac_teacher-talk>more time</ac_teacher-talk>. Provide concrete examples as needed.</ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_1" index="3">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Challenge</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Ask children to describe how the sky changes from early morning, when we wake up, to nighttime, when it’s time for bed. Ask them when they see the sun and when they see the moon and stars.  </ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </differentiation-section>      <modifications-section>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_1" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Modifications</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_1" index="2">
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Oral Language Support</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Provide additional opportunities throughout the day for English language learners to hear and use words that describe the passage of time, including sequence words such as <ac_teacher-talk>first, next, then, later, last, before, during,</ac_teacher-talk> and <ac_teacher-talk>after;</ac_teacher-talk> words that describe the time of day such as <ac_teacher-talk>in the morning, at noontime, in the evening,</ac_teacher-talk> and <ac_teacher-talk>at night;</ac_teacher-talk> and the words <ac_teacher-talk>yesterday, today, tomorrow; last week;</ac_teacher-talk> and <ac_teacher-talk>next week.</ac_teacher-talk></ac_teacher-card-body>
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Attention Support</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Previewing the day’s activities can help children to focus. Begin each day by discussing with children what they will be doing. Use sequence words to describe the day’s schedule.</ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </modifications-section>      <copyright-section>
        <section-block type="copyright_b_1" index="1">
          <ac_back_copyright_line>
            <isbn>978-1-338-65577-3</isbn>. TM ® &amp; © Scholastic Inc. All rights reserved.</ac_back_copyright_line>
        </section-block>
      </copyright-section>    </ac_card-1_back>  </ac_card-1>  <ac_card-2 day="2">    <ac_card-2_front>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_f_2" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>WE WILL PERSIST!</ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <instructions>
        <section-block type="instructions_f_2" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Instructions</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>        <before-section>
          <section-block type="before_f_2" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Gather Materials </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> Gather the Vocabulary Cards <ac_teacher-talk>goals</ac_teacher-talk> and <ac_teacher-talk>solve problems,</ac_teacher-talk> along with the Activity Cards.</ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Connect to Large Group  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>
              <ac_teacher-speaking>Today we read the book <ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue>How Kids Grow.</ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue> We learned about persistence, which is what we need to reach our goal, even if something is hard. To learn new things, we keep practicing. We also need persistence when we solve problems. Figuring out how to make a big building with blocks can be hard. It may fall down a lot until we know where to put the blocks. We learn how to make it strong by persisting. When we don’t give up, we learn new and exciting things. </ac_teacher-speaking></ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Explain the Activity  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>
              <ac_teacher-speaking>In this activity, we will look at pictures of people doing different activities and talk about the persistence Mind Builder.</ac_teacher-speaking>
            </ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Teach/Model  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>
              <ac_teacher-speaking>Let’s look at this first card. What do we see? What is this girl learning to do? Why do we need persistence in order to learn how to ride a bike? </ac_teacher-speaking>   </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </before-section>        <during-section>
          <section-block type="during_f_2" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>Review the Vocabulary Cards for the words <ac_teacher-talk>goals</ac_teacher-talk> and<ac_teacher-talk> solve problems. </ac_teacher-talk>
            </ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Ask</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  Show the first picture card and ask the question on the back of the card. Offer extra challenge or support as needed.</ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Extend </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> Use the last question on the back of the card to extend conversation.</ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Repeat  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Continue the activity with the other picture cards.  </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </during-section>        <after-section>
          <section-block type="after_f_2" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Talk About Persistence </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> Encourage children to talk about things they have persisted in. Ask: <ac_teacher-speaking>Have you ever had a goal to learn something new? What did you want to learn? Was it hard? Did you have to keep trying? What do you think would have happened if you had given up? </ac_teacher-speaking>
            </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </after-section>      </instructions>    </ac_card-2_front>    <ac_card-2_back>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_b_2" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>WE WILL PERSIST!</ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <differentiation-section>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_2" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Differentiation</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_2" index="2">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Support</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Revisit the Vocabulary Cards <ac_teacher-talk>goals</ac_teacher-talk> and <ac_teacher-talk>solve problems</ac_teacher-talk> to check children’s understanding. Ask for volunteers to describe their experiences. Discuss the tasks of training a dog and balancing on a beam. Have children act out each task.</ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_2" index="3">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Challenge</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Encourage children to respond in complete sentences and to use the words <ac_teacher-talk>persist, goals,</ac_teacher-talk> and <ac_teacher-talk>solve problems. </ac_teacher-talk>Invite children to give other examples of when they had to persist to learn something new. </ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </differentiation-section>      <modifications-section>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_2" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Modifications</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_2" index="1">
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Multilingual Learners</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Multiple-meaning words can be challenging for multilingual learners. Children might think of the meaning of <ac_teacher-talk>train</ac_teacher-talk> as a locomotive but may not know the word when used in the context of <ac_teacher-talk>training</ac_teacher-talk> a pet. Similarly, they may know what <ac_teacher-talk>string</ac_teacher-talk> is, but they may not understand <ac_teacher-talk>string</ac_teacher-talk> as a verb, as in <ac_teacher-talk>stringing</ac_teacher-talk> wooden beads. Assist children in learning multiple meanings of English words by using words in various contexts and providing opportunities for children to use the words in their own speech.</ac_teacher-card-body>
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Speech and Language Support</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Repetition of vocabulary is an important component of helping children develop language and increase vocabulary. Keep an easy-to-access list of previously taught vocabulary words. Glance at the list each day and find opportunities to revisit those words.  </ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </modifications-section>                  <copyright-section>
        <section-block type="copyright_b_2" index="1">
          <ac_back_copyright_line>
            <isbn>978-1-338-65577-3</isbn>. TM ® &amp; © Scholastic Inc. All rights reserved.</ac_back_copyright_line>
        </section-block>
      </copyright-section>    </ac_card-2_back>  </ac_card-2>  <ac_card-3 day="3">    <ac_card-3_front>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_f_3" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>OUR FAMILIES</ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <instructions>
        <section-block type="instructions_f_3" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Instructions</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>        <before-section>
          <section-block type="before_f_3" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Connect to Large Group  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>
              <ac_teacher-speaking>Today we read the book <ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue>How Kids Grow.</ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue> We saw how mothers cuddle their babies. We also saw how Steven, a one-year-old boy, learned to say “Mama” and “Papa” and even to call the family dog “Da.” </ac_teacher-speaking></ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Explain the Activity  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>
              <ac_teacher-speaking>In this activity, we will look at pictures of different families and talk about what we see. Do we see children? Babies? Grandparents? Sisters? Brothers? Pets? Think about your own family while we talk about the pictures. How is your family like the family in the picture? How is your family like no other family?</ac_teacher-speaking>
            </ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Teach/Model  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>
              <ac_teacher-talk>Let’s look at this first card. What do we see? How many adults are in this family? How many children are in this family? Who is the oldest child? How can you tell?    </ac_teacher-talk>
            </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </before-section>        <during-section>
          <section-block type="during_f_3" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Ask </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> Show the next picture card and ask the question on the back of the card, offering extra challenge or support as needed.</ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Extend  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Use the last question on the back of the card to extend conversation.</ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Repeat  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Continue the activity using the following picture cards.  </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </during-section>        <after-section>
          <section-block type="after_f_3" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Talk About Our Families </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed> Encourage children to discuss how their families are the same as the families in the pictures and how they are different. How many brothers and sisters do they have? Are there any babies? Do they have a pet? What do they like to do with their family? Encourage discussion. Emphasize that families are all different and that all kinds of families are okay.  </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </after-section>      </instructions>    </ac_card-3_front>    <ac_card-3_back>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_b_3" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>OUR FAMILIES</ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <differentiation-section>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_3" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Differentiation</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_3" index="2">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Support</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Check children’s understanding of <ac_teacher-talk>adults</ac_teacher-talk>. Encourage children to explain how they can tell who the grandparents are in the pictures. How do we know someone is older? Use the words <ac_teacher-talk>baby, child, adult, </ac_teacher-talk>and <ac_teacher-talk>elderly</ac_teacher-talk> to describe people of different ages.</ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_3" index="3">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Challenge</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Ask children to describe different family relationships. Check understanding of the concept of grandparents (that they are the parents of your mother or father), aunts, uncles, and cousins. </ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </differentiation-section>      <modifications-section>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_3" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Modifications</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_3" index="2">
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Multilingual Learners</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Encourage children’s families to visit the classroom and share their customs, music, and traditions. You may want to invite families to each bring a favorite dish, checking first for food allergies or prohibitions. Make a point of trying each family’s contribution, remarking positively on the taste, and asking about the ingredients or preparation.</ac_teacher-card-body>
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Attention Support</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Self-talk is an important skill that we often use as adults to walk ourselves through solving problems. If, for example, you discovered your car had a flat tire, you might say to yourself, “Okay. Stay calm. What do I do next?” You can teach this skill to children by modeling self-talk as you think aloud about a simple problem. Encourage children to talk as they think.</ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </modifications-section>                  <copyright-section>
        <section-block type="copyright_b_3" index="1">
          <ac_back_copyright_line>
            <isbn>978-1-338-65577-3</isbn>. TM ® &amp; © Scholastic Inc. All rights reserved.</ac_back_copyright_line>
        </section-block>
      </copyright-section>    </ac_card-3_back>  </ac_card-3>  <ac_card-4 day="4">    <ac_card-4_front>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_f_4" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>LIVING OR NONLIVING?</ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <instructions>
        <section-block type="instructions_f_4" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Instructions</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>        <before-section>
          <section-block type="before_f_4" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Connect to Large Group  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>
              <ac_teacher-speaking>Today we read the informational poster <ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue>What We Have Learned.</ac_teacher-speaking_emphasis_blue> We certainly have learned a lot this year! We’ve learned about living things, like animals and plants, and we’ve learned about objects that are not alive, like trucks and cars and books.</ac_teacher-speaking> Discuss what makes something living or nonliving. Elicit from children that living things grow and to grow they need food and water and air. </ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Explain the Activity  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>
              <ac_teacher-speaking>In this activity, we will look at pictures and sort them into two groups: Living Things and Nonliving Things.</ac_teacher-speaking></ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Teach/Model  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>
              <ac_teacher-speaking>Let’s look at this card. What do you see? Are rocks living or nonliving? Have children name some other common objects to confirm their understanding of the concept.     </ac_teacher-speaking>
            </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </before-section>        <during-section>
          <section-block type="during_f_4" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>Tape a line down the center of the table. Using different-color markers, label one side of the line “living” and the other side “nonliving.” </ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Ask</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  As children identify each card, have them place it on the appropriate side of the dividing line. </ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Extend  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Use the last question on the back of the card to extend conversation.</ac_teacher-card-body>
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Concept Sort  </ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Have children sort the cards into two groups: “living things” and “nonliving things.”  </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </during-section>        <after-section>
          <section-block type="after_f_4" index="1">
            <ac_teacher-card-body>
              <ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>Talk About Living Things</ac_teacher-card_run-in_hed>  Remind children that living things grow. Review what all living things need: food, water, and air. To extend the concept, provide magazines and have children cut out pictures of living and nonliving things and place them on the table in the correct group.  </ac_teacher-card-body>
          </section-block>
        </after-section>      </instructions>    </ac_card-4_front>    <ac_card-4_back>      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_b_4" index="1">
          <ac_header-game-card>LIVING OR NONLIVING?</ac_header-game-card>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>      <differentiation-section>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_4" index="1">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Differentiation</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_4" index="2">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Support</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Before you begin, have children repeat the words <ac_teacher-talk>living</ac_teacher-talk> and <ac_teacher-talk>nonliving</ac_teacher-talk>. Have them give an example of something that is living and something that is nonliving. </ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="differentiation_b_4" index="1">
          <ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>Challenge</ac_diff_support-challenge_heds>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Ask children to identify living things found outside. If they go to the playground, what might they see that is living? What is nonliving? How might using a magnifier help us investigate living and nonliving things?</ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </differentiation-section>      <modifications-section>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_4" index="2">
          <ac_teacher-card_hed>Modifications</ac_teacher-card_hed>
        </section-block>
        <section-block type="modifications_b_4" index="1">
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Multilingual Learners</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Invite volunteers to teach the class the names of two different animals in their home language. Spanish speakers may choose cognates, such as <ac_teacher-talk>elefante</ac_teacher-talk> (elephant), <ac_teacher-talk>león</ac_teacher-talk> (lion), or <ac_teacher-talk>tigre</ac_teacher-talk> (tiger), although many animal names are not cognates in Spanish—for example, <ac_teacher-talk>perro</ac_teacher-talk> (dog), <ac_teacher-talk>pato</ac_teacher-talk> (duck), <ac_teacher-talk>caballo</ac_teacher-talk> (horse), and <ac_teacher-talk>vaca</ac_teacher-talk> (cow). Then ask them to name two nonliving items in their home language and teach these words to their classmates. </ac_teacher-card-body>
          <ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>Attention Support</ac_mod_teacher-card_d_hed>
          <ac_teacher-card-body>Providing immediate and predictable incentives for positive behavior can help keep fidgety children engaged. Incorporate the word <ac_teacher-talk>goals</ac_teacher-talk>—introduced on Day 2—by helping children establish a goal for the activity. You can offer children stickers for meeting a specific and well-defined behavioral goal, such as cutting out four pictures and placing them with the correct group on the table.</ac_teacher-card-body>
        </section-block>
      </modifications-section>                  <copyright-section>
        <section-block type="copyright_b_4" index="1">
          <ac_back_copyright_line>
            <isbn>978-1-338-65577-3</isbn>. TM ® &amp; © Scholastic Inc. All rights reserved.</ac_back_copyright_line>
        </section-block>
      </copyright-section>    </ac_card-4_back>  </ac_card-4>            </teacher-activity-cards>
