<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<flip-chart lang="en">
  <flip_chart-28 day="4">
    <flip_chart-28_front>
      <graphic href="EC3-5_Flipchart_T7W4_YouCanHelp.jpg"/>
    </flip_chart-28_front>
    <flip_chart-28_back>
      <masthead>
        <section-block type="masthead_b_1" index="1">
          <flip_chart-theme-text>Our Earth</flip_chart-theme-text>
          <flip_chart-topic-text>Protect the Earth</flip_chart-topic-text>
          <flip_chart-concept-question>How can we care for our world? </flip_chart-concept-question>
        </section-block>
      </masthead>
      <display-head-section>
        <section-block type="display_b_1" index="1">
          <flip_chart-display-head>YOU CAN HELP</flip_chart-display-head>
        </section-block>
      </display-head-section>
      <teacher-facing-section>
        <section-block type="teacher-facing_b_1" index="1">
          <flip_chart-teacher-facing-content-box>
            <flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Earth is our home. It gives us food to eat, water to drink, and air to breathe. It gives us lakes to swim in, trees to sit under, and flowers to enjoy. It’s important to take care of our home. We need to keep it clean. We also need to make sure we don’t waste the important gifts Earth gives us.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>What can you do to take care of Earth? You can do a lot.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-head>Turn Off the Lights</flip_chart-teacher-facing-head><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Lights are very useful when we need them to see in the dark. But turning them off when we don’t need them is one way to take care of Earth. </flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Lights use electricity. The more electricity we save, the healthier Earth is. So, turn off the lights when you don’t need them. You can also turn off other things that use electricity, like computers and televisions. Every little bit helps!</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-head>Save Water</flip_chart-teacher-facing-head><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Water is one of the most important gifts Earth gives us, because we need water to live. We drink it when we’re thirsty. We use it to take baths and to wash our clothes. We use it to water the crops we grow for food. Animals need water, too.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>How can you help save water? Turn off the faucet when you are not using the water. Next time, turn the water off as you brush your teeth. You will save lots of water! Think of how much water we could save if everyone did that!</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-head>Reuse and Recycle</flip_chart-teacher-facing-head><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>Too much trash hurts Earth. How can we make less trash? We can find ways to reuse things instead of throwing them away. We can also recycle things, so they can be turned into something new instead of being thrown away.</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>When you reuse boxes or bottles for crafts and other projects, you find a new use for them instead of putting them into the trash. It’s fun using our imaginations to dream of new ways to use old things!</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph><flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>When you recycle paper, the old paper you used can be turned into new paper! Recycling works for cans, plastic, and other materials, too!</flip_chart-teacher-facing-paragraph>
          </flip_chart-teacher-facing-content-box>
        </section-block>
      </teacher-facing-section>
      <copyright-section>
        <section-block type="copyright_b_1" index="1">
          <flip_chart-credit-line>Photos ©: clockwise from top: MIA Studio/Shutterstock, DGLimages/Shutterstock, Rawpixel.com/Shutterstock, Neja Hrovat/Shutterstock, Modxka/Shutterstock, bysora/Shutterstock. Background art by Wook Jin Jung for Scholastic Inc.</flip_chart-credit-line>
        </section-block>
      </copyright-section>
    </flip_chart-28_back>
  </flip_chart-28>
</flip-chart>
